Terms of Service / Privacy Policy
=================================

Terms of Service
================

### 1\. Terms

By accessing the website at [https://ygorganization.com](https://ygorganization.com/), you are agreeing to be bound by these terms of service, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this website are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.

### 2\. Use License

Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on YGOrganization’s website for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not:  
modify or copy the materials;  
use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);  
attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on YGOrganization’s website;  
remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or  
transfer the materials to another person or “mirror” the materials on any other server.  
This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by YGOrganization at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.

### 3\. Disclaimer

The materials on YGOrganization’s website are provided on an ‘as is’ basis. YGOrganization makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties including, without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights.  
Further, YGOrganization does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its website or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.

### 4\. Limitations

In no event shall YGOrganization or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on YGOrganization’s website, even if YGOrganization or a YGOrganization authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.

### 5\. Accuracy of materials

The materials appearing on YGOrganization’s website could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. YGOrganization does not warrant that any of the materials on its website are accurate, complete or current. YGOrganization may make changes to the materials contained on its website at any time without notice. However YGOrganization does not make any commitment to update the materials.

### 6\. Links

YGOrganization has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its website and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by YGOrganization of the site. Use of any such linked website is at the user’s own risk.

### 7\. Modifications

YGOrganization may revise these terms of service for its website at any time without notice. By using this website you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these terms of service.

### 8\. Governing Law

These terms and conditions are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Canada and you irrevocably submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in that State or location.

==========================

Your privacy is important to us.

It is YGOrganization’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. Accordingly, we have developed this privacy policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and otherwise make use of personal information. We have outlined our privacy policy below.

We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.  
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.  
We will collect and use personal information solely for fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other ancillary purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.  
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.  
We will protect personal information by using reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.  
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.  
We will only retain personal information for as long as necessary for the fulfilment of those purposes.  
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. YGOrganization may change this privacy policy from time to time at YGOrganization’s sole discretion.

### Third Party Ad Servers

YGOrganization uses third-party advertising companies and advertising networks to deliver advertisements on the website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address or email address) about your visits to this or other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, go to [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.) Policies provided by our third-party advertising companies can be reviewed here: [https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/6008942?hl=en&visit\_id=1-636674476335053234-2484224167&rd=1.](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/6008942?hl=en&visit_id=1-636674476335053234-2484224167&rd=1)

By visiting YGOrganization, you consent to the usage and collection (if any) of information as defined above.

### Common ID Cookie

This site uses cookies and similar tracking technologies such as the Common ID cookie to provide its services. Cookies are important devices for measuring advertising effectiveness and ensuring a robust online advertising industry. The Common ID cookie stores a unique user id in the first party domain and is accessible to our ad partners. This simple ID that can be utilized to improve user matching, especially for delivering ads to iOS and MacOS browsers. Users can opt out of the Common ID tracking cookie by clicking [here](#).

### Advertising Privacy Settings

When you use our site, pre-selected companies may access and use certain information on your device and about your interests to serve ads or personalized content. You may revisit or change consent-choices at any time by clicking here.

### Mediavine Programmatic Advertising (Ver 1.1)

The Website works with Mediavine to manage third-party interest-based advertising appearing on the Website. Mediavine serves content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use first and third-party cookies. A cookie is a small text file which is sent to your computer or mobile device (referred to in this policy as a “device”) by the web server so that a website can remember some information about your browsing activity on the Website.

First party cookies are created by the website that you are visiting. A third-party cookie is frequently used in behavioral advertising and analytics and is created by a domain other than the website you are visiting. Third-party cookies, tags, pixels, beacons and other similar technologies (collectively, “Tags”) may be placed on the Website to monitor interaction with advertising content and to target and optimize advertising. Each internet browser has functionality so that you can block both first and third-party cookies and clear your browser’s cache. The “help” feature of the menu bar on most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to receive notification of new cookies, how to disable existing cookies and how to clear your browser’s cache. For more information about cookies and how to disable them, you can consult the information at [All About Cookies](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/).

Without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of the Website content and features. Please note that rejecting cookies does not mean that you will no longer see ads when you visit our Site. In the event you opt-out, you will still see non-personalized advertisements on the Website.

The Website collects the following data using a cookie when serving personalized ads:

* IP Address
* Operating System type
* Operating System version
* Device Type
* Language of the website
* Web browser type
* Email (in hashed form)

Mediavine Partners (companies listed below with whom Mediavine shares data) may also use this data to link to other end user information the partner has independently collected to deliver targeted advertisements. Mediavine Partners may also separately collect data about end users from other sources, such as advertising IDs or pixels, and link that data to data collected from Mediavine publishers in order to provide interest-based advertising across your online experience, including devices, browsers and apps. This data includes usage data, cookie information, device information, information about interactions between users and advertisements and websites, geolocation data, traffic data, and information about a visitor’s referral source to a particular website. Mediavine Partners may also create unique IDs to create audience segments, which are used to provide targeted advertising.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices to opt-in or opt-out of this data collection, please visit [National Advertising Initiative opt out page](https://thenai.org/opt-out/). You may also visit [Digital Advertising Alliance website](http://optout.aboutads.info/#/) and [Network Advertising Initiative website](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#) to learn more information about interest-based advertising. You may download the AppChoices app at [Digital Advertising Alliance’s AppChoices app](https://youradchoices.com/appchoices) to opt out in connection with mobile apps, or use the platform controls on your mobile device to opt out.

For specific information about Mediavine Partners, the data each collects and their data collection and privacy policies, please visit [Mediavine Partners](https://www.mediavine.com/ad-partners/).

##### Recent Posts

#### [More Quarter Century Bonanza Reprints \[TCG\]](https://ygorganization.com/more-quarter-century-bonanza-reprints-tcg/)

October 30, 2024

#### [CDP: Supreme King Odd-Eyes Performapal Magician with Odd-Eyes Solblaze Dragon](https://ygorganization.com/cdp_pendulumnominon/)

October 30, 2024

#### [Reinforce Your Frontline With “Support Unit – Kumamimi”! \[RD/KP19\]](https://ygorganization.com/reinforce-your-frontline-with-support-unit-kumamimi-rd-kp19/)

October 30, 2024

#### [Various Contents of Quarter Century Bonanza \[TCG\]](https://ygorganization.com/various-contents-of-quarter-century-bonanza-tcg/)

October 30, 2024

#### [Legendary Lord Six Samurai – Shi En Playmat \[TCG\]](https://ygorganization.com/legendary-lord-six-samurai-shi-en-playmat-tcg/)

October 30, 2024

* [\[email protected\]](https://ygorganization.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

© 2024 YGOrganization. All rights reserved.

 Submit

Type above and press _Enter_ to search. Press _Esc_ to cancel.
